<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--  Copyright (C) 2013 - 2014 Alexander "Evisceration" Martinz

 This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
 the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
 (at your option) any later version.

 This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
 GNU General Public License for more details.

 You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
 along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
-->
<resources>
    <string name="sorry">Sorry!</string>
    <string name="no_help">No help for this section available! You are on your own ;)</string>
    <string name="total_state_time_help">The total time of all cpu states together. Normally this is equal to the uptime of your device / time since last reboot.</string>
    <string name="time_in_state_help">The time of how long the cpu stayed in a specific state. States are the frequencies of your cpu together with special states like \"Deep Sleep\".</string>
    <string name="unused_cpu_states_help">Lists the states your cpu is supporting, but hasn\'t spent any time in.</string>
    <string name="max_freq_help">The maximum clock that the CPU can use. Reduce this frequency for better battery life at cost of performance.</string>
    <string name="min_freq_help">The minimum clock that the CPU can use. Reduce this frequency for better battery life at cost of performance. If you experience audio stuttering etc while your screen is off, try increasing it.</string>
    <string name="governor_help">The governor controls the scaling of the CPU frequencies depending on CPU load.</string>
    <string name="io_help">I/O Scheduling is the method that operating systems use to decide in which priority I/O operations will be submitted to storage volumes. I/O Scheduling is sometimes also called disk scheduling.</string>
    <string name="gpu_freq_max_help">The maximum clock that the GPU can use. Reduce this frequency for better battery life at cost of performance.</string>
    <string name="gpu_gov_help">The governor for the gpu. Please note that some default governors are listed, which do not have to exist! If they exist, the value will stick.</string>
    <string name="mpdecision_help">MPDecision is a proprietary Qualcomm daemon that makes calls to the SoC to manage the cpu cores.\nWARNING: Only stop if you have a valid hotplug replacement like Intelli-Plug!</string>
    <string name="intelli_plug_help">Intelli-Plug is a replacement for Qualcomm\'s proprietary MPDecision, which runs in userspace. It is done in kernel instead in userspace which is faster as in userspace it has to poll the kernel.</string>
    <string name="intelli_plug_eco_help">Eco Mode is a optimized dual core solution for quadcore CPU \'s. This should allow for maximum battery life without sacrificing performance.</string>
    <string name="powersaving_sched_mc_help">Tries to group tasks on a core until it reaches its maximum load and powers on the next core.\nIf enabled, it sacrifices power in exchange for battery life.</string>
    <string name="msm_dcvs_help">Enable support for MSM DCVS to control all CPU and GPU core frequencies. The DCVS manager allows idle driver to feed the idle information to the algorithm and the algorithm returns a frequency for the core which is passed to the frequency change driver.</string>
    <string name="tasklist_help">MPDecision may override CPU/GPU actions and thus they may not work, if MPDecision is running!</string>
    <string name="fstrim_help">FStrim is used on a mounted filesystem to discard (or \"trim\") blocks which are not in use by the filesystem.\nThis can help reducing lags and keep performance of your device.</string>
    <string name="reapply_on_boot_help">Restores the changes you did when the device is booting up.</string>
    <string name="extensive_logging_help">Should be used only for debugging purposes.\nLogs extra information to the logcat.</string>
</resources>
